Your reaction when you heard that your grandfather shot Ralph Yarl for ringing his doorbell?
Myself and my family stand with Ralph Yarl and seeking justice.
Why are you speaking out and apparently against your grandfather?
He had to know his grandbaby with the cornrows was definitely going to speak out against him.
It's the right thing to do. This country happens over and over again where people get away with
killing unarmed innocent black people. People need to speak out and not making excuses for
this kind of behavior and this violence. Do you believe your grandfather is racist?
I believe he holds racist tendencies. I feel like a lot of people of that generation are
caught up in this 24-hour news cycle of fear and paranoia. Sit and watch Fox News all day,
every day, blaring in his living room. And I think that stuff really kind of reinforces this
negative view of minority groups and reinforces and galvanizes racist people. He was a huge
Trump supporter. And between that and then the galvanizing that people have been feeling lately
with the politicians and ideologues, co-signing domestic terrorism, and even pardoning people
who murder other people for differing political beliefs. I feel like all that stuff has really
radicalized him a little bit. I know a racist face when I see one. I be knowing.